[ film reel ticking ]
[ water splashing ]
May I ask you something ?
I can 't promise I 'll answer .
R ... right , that 's exactly what I meant .
Um , are you allowed to speak along the way ?
I was thinking there might be rules .
Let me put it this way
very few make it all the way without uttering a word .
People are overcome with a strange and sudden need
to confess on these trips .
And not all of it can be said to be
of great rhetorical quality
but do carry on merrily
just don 't believe you 're going to tell me something
I haven 't heard before .
[ instrumental music ]
I will tentatively divide my tale
into five randomly chosen incidents
over a twelve-year period .
So I 'm standing here holding this jack
crap 's not working .
Do you , uh , do you have a jack I could borrow ?
No , I 'm sorry .
- No ? - No
[ sighs ]
That 's odd , I thought everyone had a jack .
I don 't .
Perhaps you could have a look at my car ?
Well , I don 't have to have a look at your car .
The issue with your jack is it 's broken .
There .
So , uh , what 's a person like me supposed to do ?
Well , I suppose
I could , uh , drive over to Sonny 's repair shop
and call for roadside assistance .
It 's about , uh , five miles from here .
What kind of repair shop is it ?
It 's ... it 's .. Sonny 's a blacksmith , very good one .
Blacksmith .
Well , maybe this Sonny can repair the jack ?
You 'd have to talk to Sonny about that .
Perhaps , I could entice you to drive me there ?
- Please . - Um ..
Oops , that was a mistake .
Mistake ?
Me getting in this car with you .
What was it one 's mother used to say
about not getting into cars with strangers ?
Well ..
I wouldn 't know what your mother said .
You might as well be a serial killer .
I 'm sorry but you do kind of look like one .
You 'd like me to drive you back to your car ?
No , no . I can take care of myself .
I 'm sorry , were you offended
that I called you a serial killer ?
No .
It 's of absolutely no importance to me .
Maybe it 's just the van .
It 's the kind one might expect to be kidnapped in
or used to transport corpses .
But if you really were a serial killer
I guess the easiest thing would be just
to bury my body back up there by those trees
but you 'd have to remember to dig six feet down
so the foxes couldn 't dig up my grave .
What would I do ?
What would I do to keep you from getting away with it ?
Of course , I 'd just
pick up that jack and hit you over the head with it .
A jack like that can do quite a bit of damage
don 't you think ?
I 'm not a medical examiner .
It 'd do quite a lot of damage .
Don 't forget this . Good luck with Sonny .
Um , would it be too much to ask for you to drive me back ?
If this Sonny is as fast as you say he is ?
I 'm sure Sonny is perfectly capable of giving you
a lift back to your ..
As ... as I told you before , I don 't like
driving with strangers .
Well , I 'm just as much of a stranger as Sonny is .
Oh , getting along just fine .
I 'll just go speak to Sonny , just take a moment .
[ whirring ]
Sonny .
Hi , Jack .
How 's it going ?
Well , I was working on Miller 's tractor
but this lady is being really persistent .
You don 't say .
Big mistake .
The reason serial killers can roam around free in our country
is that they have no connection between themselves
and their victims .
So , you just made a big mistake
letting Sonny see the two of us together .
[ panting ]
You know ..
... honestly , I have more important things
to be doing with my life
than messing around with this crap .
You ... you said he was really good .
Yeah , well , I 'm sure Sonny was just
distracted by your goddamned blabbering .
Now I have to go , I have an appointment .
Appointment , what appointment ?
That 's none of your goddamn business now , is it ?
You 're not just gonna leave me here .
In fact , yes , that is kind of what I was thinking .
I 'm sure there will be another serial killer passing by
who can give you a lift back to Sonny 's .
That is , unless he decides to kill you first .
[ chuckling ]
Even if I was to beg you to drive me back ?
Just a last time ?
Pretty please .
[ tapping ]
[ sighs ]
You know , I take it all back
what I said earlier about you looking like a serial killer .
No , no , no , you don 't have the disposition
for that sort of thing .
You 're way too much of a wimp to murder anyone .
[ piano music ]
[ humming ]
Oh , dear , you are a dangerous man
smacked her with a jack , did you ?
Honestly , I 've heard of more murders
than I can count .
And by the way , what does this ridiculous man
have to do with anything ?
It 's Glenn Gould
one of the greatest piano players of our time .
He represents art .
[ piano music ]
So a jack in the face of
an admittedly unbearable lady was great art .
Is that what I 'm to make of it ?
Dear Mr. Verge , please give me a chance
to cast some supplemental light on the story of the jack .
The old cathedrals often have sublime artworks hidden away
in the darkest corners for only God to see
or whatever one feels like calling
the great architect behind it all .
The same goes for murder .
When I say cathedrals
it is first and foremost the gothic buildings we admire .
Here elegant , pointed arches have replaced the earlier
more primitive rounded arches .
The art of engineering is first and foremost about statics
that is so things remain standing in spite of
the various forces that impact the buildings .
In this way , the pointed arch created a possibility to build
much higher and with much more light
but most importantly with less use of material .
I often say that the material does the work .
In other words it has a kind of will of its own
and by following it , the result will be
the most exquisite .
So the material was the jack
and it jumped into the lady 's face on its own .
Art is many things .
Very convenient and unusual
in the pile of bad excuses .
But all of that is of no interest whatsoever
unless you 're an engineer .
I am an engineer .
[ piano music ]
My mother was of the opinion that becoming an engineer
was the more financially viable choice
but my really big dream was to become an architect .
Right before the lady and the jack
I purchased a building lot
and since I was my own developer
due to a substantial inheritance
no one could keep me from drawing up
my own plans for my own house .
Engineer or architect
what I see is an OCD patient in full bloom .
Ordnungszwang Jack
to use a good German word .
Yes , perhaps , it is in any case true
that I suffered from compulsions as a child .
I was completely hysterical about cleaning
and could never leave a room that wasn 't
perfectly neat and clean .
A standard that was difficult to maintain
in the walk-in freezer .
The walk-in freezer ?
The walk-in freezer on Prospect Avenue .
The sign has been broken for forever
so no one really knew what the name of the street was .
I bought the pizzas from the former owner
of the walk-in freezer .
He claimed it was a great deal
but of course I never managed to sell them
so it all became too much for me .
I only ate one of those shitty pizzas .
Pizza , pizza !
[ speaking in foreign language ]
And then there was a door to another room
which I never managed to open .
A fucking neurotic riddled with obsessive compulsions
and a pathetic dream of something greater .
[ whirring ]
And what about the police ?
I imagine they started coming around a lot .
No , call it luck if you will .
I had attempted to hide her car ..
... but to my great annoyance
you could still catch a glimpse of it from the main road .
You know , without realizing where I had parked the car
was a stroke of genius .
You see , the small brook defines the state border
and the local police , per definition
can 't see across state lines .
It 's not their jurisdiction .
So I had no inquiries from the police .
And by the way , I don 't even know if Sonny
had told them about me .
We met up quite a few times since
but never spoke of it .
[ door closes ]
[ doorbell ringing ]
Hang on .
Hi .
Who are you ?
Police .
Did something happen ?
Oh , no , no , no
luckily nothing exactly has happened as of yet .
I understand that you are fond of
shopping at Carlson 's Supermarket .
Why ? Did something happen at Carlson 's ?
No , uh , however we 'd like to , uh , prevent
things from happening to businesses in the vicinity
like Carlson 's Supermarket .
Yeah , may ... may , may I come in ?
I 'd like to see a police badge .
So would I.
Unfortunately , that today
is going to be a bit of a problem .
Now , ahem ..
... I can tell by your expression
that you think it 's a bad thing
that I don 't have my police badge on me .
Right .
Well , I 'm here to tell you that
it 's a , it 's a good thing ..
... for the police department
and I 'm not going to lie to you , okay ?
It also happens to be a good thing for me
on a personal level . Yeah .
You see my ... my badge
it 's , uh , at the silversmith .
Yeah , it 's at the , the silversmith .
They 're ... they 're shining it up and , ah ..
... adding a few additional citations to it .
I 've been promoted .
- Okay . - Right .
So now you 're ..
Now ... now what are you ?
Like , what 's your , what 's your rank now ?
We 're not at liberty to discuss that .
Ah , that 's considered classified information .
However , I think this is safe to say that
it 's a considerable ..
... leap up the ladder .
- Uh , ahem , now may I ... - No .
Not without a badge .
[ applauding ]
Bravo , bravo , bravo , that 's excellent .
That 's exactly just the type of response we like to see .
- You say no , that makes my day . - Right .
Of course , everybody 's always talking about security
but what ... what is actually anybody doing about it ?
No , is quite the correct answer .
Yeah , it 's quite the correct answer indeed .
Of course you 'll never allow somebody in your home
just because they say , " Oh , I 'm a police officer . "
No . No , no , no . You don 't do that .
No .
You wait until they show you the proper ..
- Badge . - Yeah . The badge .
- Yup . - That 's correct . Yeah .
Um ..
May I , uh , ask you a ..
... ah , somewhat personal question ?
Um , when exactly
was it that you lost your , your husband ?
It was just over six months ago
that my husband passed ..
Where are you going with this ?
Oh , I 'm just thinking about your ..
Your pension , yeah .
I bet with a simple phone call to one of my colleagues
down in headquarters , I could get you a , ah ..
... considerable increase in your pension .
I bet that I could , I could double
what you 're currently receiving .
Wait a minute .
You could get me double my pension
from the police department by calling people ?
Uh , forgive me , uh , uh ..
... I , I 've tricked you , a bit .
In fact , as it , as it stands
I 'm not , I 'm not a police officer .
What ?
I 'm an insurance agent , lady .
The , the whole story that I told you about the badge
that 's , t-that 's something that we 've been asked to do
by the authorities , it 's , it 's for statistical
purposes or something .
[ car horn honk ]
- Hi , Glenn . - Hi , Claire .
- It 's my friend Glenn . - Glenn . Yeah , great guy .
- You know Glenn ? - Yeah , sure .
Uh , listen , are you interested
in this , this increase , uh , the money ?
Well , if you can double it .
It won 't take more than a few minutes of your time .
Alright , listen , you can come in .
This damn door sticks .
I mean , what the heck 's the worst that could happen
as long as you can double my pension .
Damn it .
Something wrong ?
[ sighs ]
This is so damn humiliating .
You know being forced to , to stand out there
exposed , time and time again
have to be put in these situations
I don 't know why .
Listen , I 'm sorry , uh , I-I .. I was jus ..
You know how humiliating it is ?
I am constantly being put in these situations .
It 's just not fair .
- No . - Do you think it 's fair ?
- No . - No .
Do you want me to get you a cup of tea ?
Nah , nah , nah . Don 't worry about it .
[ grunting ]
Ow ! Fuck .
Ow ! Fuck . Ah , fuck . Fuck .
The hell do you think you 're going ?
[ grunting ]
[ choking ]
[ groaning ]
[ grunting ]
[ panting ]
[ choking ]
Oh , no . Oh , no .
Here .
Put this under your head .
[ choking ]
I 'm sorry . Ow .
[ groaning ]
[ crying ]
I 'm so sorry .
[ groaning ]
Oh ..
[ choking ]
What can I do to make this good again ?
- What can I do ? - Ugh !
How can I help you ?
What can I do to make it better ?
[ choking ]
- Speak to me ? - Talk ..
- Can 't talk ? Okay . - Can 't .
[ Jack panting ]
[ grunts ]
Hold on a second .
I have something else I think you 're gonna like quite a bit .
[ exhales ] Do you like donuts ?
[ groaning ]
Shh .
[ groans ]
[ gasping ]
Have here ..
[ gasps ]
Here we go .
[ gasping ]
Yes , chamomile .
It 's good for you .
[ grunting ]
Jesus Chri ..
[ panting ]
[ grunts ]
[ dramatic music ]
[ engine revving ]
[ sighs ]
[ car door creaks ]
[ exhales ]
[ water running ]
[ sighs ]
[ dramatic music ]
A murderer with OCD .
It 's almost ridiculous
but how unfortunate for you , Jack .
And to top it off , with cleaning compulsions .
[ sighs ]
[ exhales ]
[ music continues ]
[ car door closes ]
[ siren wailing ]
Shit .
[ wailing continues ]
[ sighs ]
[ engine starts ]
[ wailing continues ]
[ sighs ]
[ music continues ]
[ wailing continues ]
[ panting ]
[ grunting ]
[ engine revving ]
[ exhales ]
[ tapping on window ]
Please get out of the car , sir .
[ sighs ]
Do you mind if I take a look in the van please , sir ?
- I 'd be a bad guy if I said no . - Alright , open her up , please .
Okay .
I 'm sorry , sir , but there 's been a minor break-in
down the street just now .
I 'd like to ask you a couple of questions
about anything you may have seen or heard , yeah ?
Glenn said you were visiting Claire .
I 'm sorry y ... you said something ab ... about a break-in ?
- Uh-huh . - Well ..
Well , unfortunately I think you 've got
a more serious problem .
Claire , she 's disappeared .
Clair Miller has disappeared ?
Yeah , I 've been , uh , sitting out here
for the last two hours in my van waiting for her .
Right .
You see , ahem , I contacted Claire
because , uh , her late husband was a dear friend of mine .
We worked together for number of years
on the railroad and , uh , I 'm a collector .
Yeah , I collect .
Uh , I collect Trax .
- Trax ? - Old issues of Trax .
It 's a , uh , publication owned by the railroad
and , uh , Jerry , uh
I know , I happen to know for a fact
that he also subscribed and was an enthusiast
such as myself .
So Claire said she 'd run inside
and see if she could rustle up
a couple of back issues for me .
She didn 't ask me in .
Right .
Better safe than sorry
when an oddball like myself just turns up , right ?
- Yeah . - Yeah , yeah .
So I knocked several times and , uh , she hasn 't answered .
Okay .
Sir , I 'm gonna ask you to stay right here .
I 'm just gonna go take a look .
[ knocking on door ]
Claire , it 's Ed .
- Maybe the door is open . - What ?
Or maybe not .
[ door creaks ]
Claire , you here ?
Claire ?
- Is she up there ? - No , she 's not up there .
Maybe she went out through the back .
I , I think I would have noticed that .
Uh , this is really , really strange .
If you ask me , I 'd say
that this needs to be thoroughly investigated .
Right , well I 'm not askin ' you .
You know , I have to say , also , that I heard
uh , some noises coming from ... the living room .
- Noises ? - Yeah , some noises .
I , I , of course , I can 't be sure
but it sounded a little bit like a ..
Like a scuffle of some kind .
Scuffle ?
No , no , no . You 're gonna have to put that back down , now .
Sir , that kind of investigation , that 's for police , don 't .
Right , right .
Sir , I 'm gonna have to ask you to leave the house .
- I 'm sorry ? - Sir , now !
- Okay . - Mm-hm .
You know , I 'm gonna do so under protest .
I , I feel like that my observations
well , they could be of use in an investigation .
As a tax-paying citizen , someone who is fully aware
of my constitutional rights .
What ?
O ... officer , please allow me to finish
I 'm just trying to be of assistance , okay ?
You 've got one minute , sir .
I would like to recommend one thing
and it 's within my right ,
that this room is inspected impeccably .
With a magnifying glass if you catch my drift .
- Get out . - Have a nice day , officer .
Get out , sir .
[ panting ]
[ sighs ]
[ engine revving ]
[ instrumental music ]
♪ Fame fame makes a man take things over ♪
♪ Fame fame lets him loose hard to swallow ♪
♪ Fame fame puts you there where things are hollow ♪
♪ Fame ♪ Fame ♪
Don 't the police officers in your story
seem exceptionally naive ?
Is that the point ?
No , but here it comes , the point that is .
I can hardly wait .
[ rain pattering ]
The great rain !
It washed away the long track from my escape .
Now , I don 't consider myself
a decidedly devoted man of faith .
Which , of course , is a totally crazy thing to say
considering our present situation
but I must admit ..
... I experienced the rain , the fiercest I have ever seen
as a kind of a blessing .
And the murder as a kind of liberation .
I felt I had a higher protector .
And in the reality you were
just a terrifying perverted Satan .
[ sniffles ]
But , did you understand , or even better , did you accept
the connection to your own personality ?
That you yourself were a psychopath ?
[ instrumental music ]
Well , I 'm not stupid .
That 's rather unusual .
The psychopath will never accept
his own diagnosis .
But I did !
For instance , the psychopath 's
lack of empathy .
I went to great lengths to fake normal empathy ..
... in order to hide amongst the masses .
[ chuckles ] Smile .
Oh , yes , yes , yes , yes .
Disappointed .
Very , very disappointed .
[ groaning ]
♪ Fame fame what you like is in the limo ♪
♪ Fame fame what you get is no tomorrow ♪
♪ Fame fame .. ♪
And the reeds ?
I was a very sensitive child ..
... profoundly afraid of playing .
For example , hide and seek .
In the case of hide
I always chose to run in near panic
into a field of reeds to hide .
I see something other than a scared kid .
I see a kid with a more mysterious goal .
The choice of the dash through the reeds was an escape
but also an open invitation to the pursuer
because of the clear path of broken reeds left behind .
Was there an element of come and catch me
in you as a child ?
Or perhaps , more importantly
in you as a person ?
Was there never a tiny grain of disappointment
about the great rain that washed away
your tracks so you couldn 't be caught ?
More like amazement ..
... when I think about all the things I 've done in my life
without it , in any way , resulting in punishment .
[ rustling ]
I loved when the men from the village
cut the meadows with their scythes .
Back then one spoke of the breath of the meadow .
Everyone working in rhythm
exhaling when they mowed , and inhaling when they pulled
the scythes back .
[ exhaling ]
[ inhaling ]
It was as if the meadow lived at its fullest
in my consciousness ..
... when I listened to its breath .
[ clanking ]
[ chirping ]
[ grunting ]
Stop that .
Stop it .
[ grunting ]
Stop it !
Experience had taught me how to strangle correctly
and for long enough .
[ panting ]
Bravo , Jack !
You certainly are clever and tough ..
... just like all the other criminals .
The fact is , when , after several more murders
I felt my OCD diminish
I started to take greater chances .
[ grunting ]
[ exhales ]
[ sighs ]
This time I was completely dissatisfied with the pictures
so I decided to take new ones .
[ panting ]
[ engine revving ]
[ exhales ]
Fuck . Fuck ! Fuck it !
[ engine revving ]
[ thud ]
[ exhales ]
[ grunting ] Shit !
It struck me like lightning from a clear sky .
Fuck !
I couldn 't resist running
that little old lady over .
It made my already rather daring plan of bringing
the first body back to the scene of the murder
in order to take some more inspired photos
a great deal more dangerous .
I now had a severely hemorrhaging body
and another body in a bizarre , frozen position on my hands .
Goddammit !
[ instrumental music ]
♪ Fame fame fame fame ♪ Fame fame ♪
Could you elaborate a little
on why the old lady had to die ?
I can 't explain it all , but perhaps I can describe it
as the kind of blood frenzy
an ermine experiences in a hen house .
Do you know Blake 's poems ..
... about the lamb and the tiger ?
I do know Blake superficially
but I 'm afraid I won 't escape a comprehensive tutorial .
[ instrumental music ]
God created both the lamb and the tiger .
The lamb represents innocence
and the tiger represents savagery .
Both parts are perfect and necessary .
The tiger lives on blood and murder
kills the lamb ..
... and that is also the artist 's nature .
You read Blake like the devil reads the Bible .
After all , the poor lamb didn 't ask to die
in order to become even the greatest art .
The lamb has been bestowed with the honor of living
forever in art , and art is divine .
But still the same red van . Now all bloody .
Somewhat reckless , I should think
if you don 't want to be found out .
Now , that 's exactly what I thought ..
... but I didn 't have the strength to change it
and besides , everything was still going remarkably well .
Sometimes the best way to hide is to not hide at all .
[ sighs ]
But now , as I said , the OCD was on decline ..
... so I took deliberate risks and didn 't remove the blood
from either the bedroom or the car .
It was actually quite liberating to reach that point .
It turned out the little old lady who was merely an accident
added a great touch of humor to my staged photographs .
And I was very pleased with the outcome .
Sophistication .
Mr. Sophistication ? Of course !
Your narcissism knows no bounds .
I sent the picture to the local paper
which usually distinguished itself by running stories
about missing , not to say , uh , stolen garden gates
and so , might do well with a story with a , you know
little more bite .
For me though , what was really sensational about the work
with the photo , it wasn 't the image
but the negative .
When I was ten years old , I discovered
that through the negative , you could see
the real inner demonic quality of the light .
The dark light .
[ intense music ]
But what about repentance , Jack ?
The ones I deal with tend to repent all over the place .
I repent nothing
no matter how long we have to walk
but I did think of something the other day .
Imagine a man walking down a street
underneath the street lamps .
Right under a light his shadow is the densest
but also the tiniest .
Then when he starts to move
his shadow grows in front of him .
The shadow becomes bigger and bigger
while it thins out and the shadow behind him
from the next lamppost emerges
and becomes shorter and shorter
until it reaches its ultimate density
as the man stands directly underneath the light .
Let 's say that the man standing
underneath the first lamppost is me
when I 've just committed a murder .
I feel strong and content .
I start to walk and the shadow in front of me grows bigger
like my pleasure , but at the same time
pain is on its way , represented by the shadow
behind me from the next lamppost
and at the midpoint between the lampposts
the pain is so great it outweighs my pleasure .
And with every step forward pleasure dissolves
and pain intensifies behind me .
Finally the pain is so unbearably intense
that I have to act , so when I reach the point
with the next lamp in zenith
I will kill again .
I know you want to be someone special , Jack
but let 's face it , this illustration can be used
for any addict 's tale of woe .
The alcoholic empties the bottle at the zenith
et cetera , et cetera .
But what about the family ?
[ instrumental music ]
I understand that your occupation didn 't leave
any room for a family in your life .
No , why ?
Well , it could be , despite everything
that speculating about this might have triggered
just a tiny bit of human feeling .
For example , a variation on what those of us less clever
might call need .
Need ? Because I never had a family ?
No , I can 't say that it did .
But the concept of family actually inspired
one of my greatest works .
[ instrumental music ]
Okay , hats for everyone
you are to keep your hats on at all times .
- Thank you . - Safety procedures .
Can we go up there , mom ?
Of course we 're gonna go up .
Smile , grumpy , it 'll be fun .
I don 't think so .
It 's for your sake we 've come all the way out here .
I told you I didn 't wanna go .
You wanna see the weapons ?
This , George , is a rifle .
This rifle has the capacity to hit its target
at a distance of several 100 yards .
And kill larger animals .
Have you killed any large animals ?
Well , yes , I have .
But that 's not something that I 'm proud of .
If I 'd killed some large animals
I 'd be proud of it .
I guess that 's where you and I differ , Georgie .
This here is a shotgun .
It 's what they call a smoothbore weapon .
This is not as precise as the rifle
but it 's more effective
when the animal is closer and moving .
You can touch it if you want .
Can I ?
Yeah .
Are we going hunting ?
No .
Hunting is such an unpleasant thing .
I used to hunt quite a bit , but I 've stopped .
Why ?
To be honest , I find hunting distasteful .
For example , if I wanted to shoot some of the crows
up in that tree , we 'd be talking about
what is known as culling , which quite simply means
you want to determine which animals you are going to allow
to live in your forest .
The crow has no value as prey
but can be culled because they are seen as something
of a threat to animals you wanna cultivate .
Culling , it 's also such an unpleasant word .
It has a tinge of ethnic cleansing about it .
The very sick and twisted act of hunting
has been ritualized
to such an unsettling degree .
The battue , for example
where a row of beaters scares the living daylight
out of an entire forest .
Not to mention the trophy parade , practiced primarily
in Europe at the end of the hunt
as a final insult
in which each species has its own traditional place .
We want to go up in the tower , mom .
Shh . George , wait .
Yep , we are going up .
Okay , George , you want to shoot ?
I 'll aim ..
... you pull the trigger .
Fire !
[ gunshot ]
Excellent !
To fell an animal of this size
you have to be sure to hit it in the vitals
which is to say here , in the area of the lungs .
As you can see , this one was hit here
in the hind quarter .
An animal could run a great distance
with an injury such as this .
That 's why typically a good hunter would have
a Schweiss-dog , that 's trained in following a blood trail
so you can track the animal down and finish the job .
Schweiss , well , that 's the word we use for blood trail .
Congratulations , young Georgie , you hit the animal .
So you had found yourself a family ?
Yes , that 's also how I like to see it .
[ classical music ]
But it 's all so much simpler with animals .
What do you mean ?
The order is important .
The hind will typically run in the front with the largest fawn
following the smallest last .
You 'd typically shoot at the deer
starting with the rear one
based on the fact that the two older animals can survive
without the young one
whereas , if you shot the mother first
and didn 't get the others
both fawns would probably not survive .
So in this manner , you then shoot the bigger fawn
and then the mother last .
[ heavy breathing ]
Stay down !
[ gunshot ]
Stop ! George !
George !
My family was moving in the wrong order .
I have always taken ethical hunting rules
very seriously .
On that point , I think of myself as a bit of a gentleman .
[ heavy breathing ]
A gentleman , really ?
Hmm .
Or a Mr. Sophistication even ?
[ gun firing ]
[ gunshot ]
[ woman screaming ]
No ! No !
[ wailing ]
[ gunshot ]
No !
[ wailing ]
George doesn 't seem to have much of an appetite .
Perhaps he 'd like some of that pie .
You know , when I was a boy , I never got enough pie .
Why don 't you do as I say ..
... and give the youngster a little piece of pie ?
It 's if have no say in the matter .
This was supposed to be an enjoyable picnic .
This has been a good day .
An excellent day .
Do you have a favorite number ?
Any number ?
Everybody has a favorite number .
Twelve .
That 's an excellent number .
Very good number indeed .
Picnic 's over .
You can go ahead .
I 'll take care of the kids .
One .
Two .
Three .
Four .
Five .
Six .
Seven .
Eight .
Nine .
Ten .
Eleven .
Twelve .
[ gunshot ]
Schweiss .
Exactly .
[ whistling ]
[ gun cocking ]
[ heavy breathing ]
[ whistling ]
[ gunshot ]
[ instrumental music ]
Do you expect me to praise you or applaud ?
You know , I 'm sad
that you 're so judgmental , Verge .
Don 't look at the acts , look at the works .
The whole notion of trophies .
No . No , no , no !
You 're constantly trying to manipulate me .
And with children
the most sensitive subject of all .
I 'm also sensitive , Verge .
I cannot sleep on a sheet with even the smallest wrinkle .
The hunt , after all , is a metaphor for love .
And that is your weakness , Jack .
So much has happened during those days
let 's call it signs in the sun and the moon
which claimed my presence for yet another work of art
and roused my aggression .
[ indistinct chatter ]
[ crowd screaming ]
First , the eclipse .
[ piano music ]
Then the volcanic eruption of Mount St. Helens
which I could see from my lot .
I had just then decided that using cinder blocks
was totally , totally wrong .
So I decided to change the material .
The divine material .
Love , Jack .
Love is also an art .
Not to mention intimacy .
[ scatting ]
The Iceman always inhaled his victims ' last breath .
Jack !
♪ Not your brain it 's just the flame ♪
♪ That burns your change to keep you ♪
♪ Insane ♪ Insane
♪ Fame ♪ Fame ♪
[ thudding ]
[ piano music ]
[ humming ]
[ instrumental music ]
Verge ?
I 'm here , Jack .
I don 't feel so good , Verge .
There 's a sour taste in my mouth .
You want me to show you the way to the next whiskey bar ?
It 's the acid you are starting to taste .
It appears at this depth .
I 'm afraid you are going to have to get used to it .
I placed Grumpy in the anteroom ..
... and left him there until rigor mortis
had disappeared .
I had a plan for little Grumpy .
What does that mean ?
Those who are really good at taxidermy
can make the animals look alive
by changing their expressions and positions
so it becomes a whole little scene .
I discovered that if I worked around rigor mortis
and worked before the corpses froze
then I could manipulate their expressions
and positions with steel wire , pins , tape
and things like that .
And then when they were frozen
remove it all and have a nearly
credible human being .
Grumpy was grumpy no more .
Was that what you were after ?
A completely credible human being ?
Without becoming too romantic , might one say
that exactly that is reminiscent
of a kind of desire for love ?
I had a romance .
Where did the crutch come from , Jack ?
You hadn 't hurt yourself , had you ?
A very useful little trick if you wish to look harmless .
In general , if you carry some luggage and a crutch
people come running to assist
and then you force them into the car with a weapon .
What does that have to do with love ?
I really had strong feelings for this one
much stronger than a psychopath should be able to have .
[ knocking on door ]
Smile .
Hey .
Talk to me .
I can 't .
I hate the way you look at me .
The way I look at you ?
Okay .
[ sobbing ]
[ telephone ringing ]
[ ringing continues ]
Can you tell me what 's on your mind now ?
I just don 't know where I 've got you .
Are you trying to leave me ?
I feel like you 're trying to leave me .
I 'm not going to leave you .
I 'm right here .
You feel that ?
I 'm right here , on the other end of the line .
[ laughing ]
Hang up for a second .
[ telephone ringing ]
- Hello . - Who am I speaking with ?
[ laughs ]
You know who you are speaking with .
You know I 'd never leave you .
Now what do you say ?
Don 't you think we deserve a drink ?
Sure .
I 'll be over shortly for cocktails .
[ laughs ]
♪ I went down
♪ To St. James Infirmary ♪
Simple ?
You know I hate it when you call me Simple .
My name is Jacqueline .
Jacqueline ?
Did old Mr. and Mrs. Simple really have that vivid an imagination ?
Jacqueline .. I bet they got that
right out of " The New York Times " crossword puzzle .
To me , your name is Simple , simple .
Hey , you 've got great tits .
Why do you always have to be so crude ?
What ..
Is that being crude ?
I don 't think I was being crude .
Have you figured out the difference between
lions and tigers ?
Tigers have stripes .
And where do they live ?
Africa ?
And the difference between an architect and an engineer ?
Architect draws houses ?
And an engineer ?
Also draws houses ?
You call that a difference ?
An engineer reads music , an architect plays music
if that 's something your limited brain can process .
Why do you always have to be so cruel ?
I 'm not completely stupid .
That fucking depends on your definition of " Completely . "
Can we just talk about something normal ?
- Like .. - Like ?
What you do , something like that ?
Information about what I do .
In simple terms that a simpleton can understand
is that right , Simple ?
Yes .
I kill .
Okay .
I 've killed 60 people .
I 'm a serial killer , Simple .
You 're weird .
I 'm weird ?
Why , because I 'm saying that I 've killed 61 people ?
You said 60 before .
If you weren 't as dumb as a fucking doorknob
you would be familiar with the term " Updated . "
Just because the number was 60 an hour ago
doesn 't mean that it can 't easily become
61 in just a couple of minutes .
Well , I 'm not dumb as a doorknob .
Maybe I haven 't read as many books as you .
Simple , come on .
You 're as dumb as fuck .
Now why don 't you be a good little dreamboat
and go get me a magic marker .
Could you bring me a magic marker ?
Red or black ?
E ... either one 's fine .
You 're fucking weird .
Excuse me .
- Officer . - Yeah .
My friend is , like , totally weird
and he said he killed 60 people
or maybe even 61 .
Have you been drinking ?
Um , yeah .
Then stop .
[ tapping ]
Everything that this woman has said ..
... is true .
I have killed 60 people !
Sixty people !
I 'm a serial killer .
Please help me .
I 've also been a horrible human being ..
... to this woman right here ..
... Ms. Jacqueline .
Miss , would you be kind enough to sweep up your friend here
and take him back inside ?
I can 't order you both to stop drinking
but I would recommend it .
[ sobbing ]
I can never make it up to you .
Never be able to make it up to you .
Can you forgive me ?
Yeah .
I forgive you .
Come on . Let 's go inside .
You need some pills .
I 've got a friend who 's got some good pills .
[ clears throat ]
Are you leaving ?
I was just gonna go get some pills .
Do you have my ... my keys ?
I 'm not gonna take some random pills .
You know , I really think I deserve better than this .
I 'm gonna hang on to the keys .
It 's a bad habit for you to
go rushing downstairs every time
we start to have , have a good time .
Right ?
You 're walking without your crutch .
And you weren 't using it downstairs either .
You 're Mr. Sophistication , aren 't you ?
If you feel like screaming ..
... I definitely think that you should .
[ screaming ]
You call that screaming ?
Help ! Help !
[ screaming ]
Help !
Yes , help !
There 's a murderer in the building !
It 's Mr. Sophistication !
Help !
[ sobbing ]
Shh !
Shh ! Hey .
Hey . Hey .
Shh !
Do you hear ?
Do you hear anything ?
Do you hear anybody running downstairs to help ?
Some neighbors you have .
You want to try the window ?
I just want my keys .
I want my keys .
Help !
Help me !
Please help me !
[ sobbing ]
[ sighs ]
You know , maybe I 'm mistaken , but ..
... as far as I can tell ..
... not a single light has gone on
in any apartment or stairwell .
You know why that is ?
' Cause in this hell of a town ..
... in this hell of a country ..
... in this hell of a world , nobody wants to help !
You can scream ..
... from now until Christmas Eve
and the only answer you 'll get
is the deafening silence that you 're hearing right now .
Can 't we talk ?
There 's a time for talking
and a time for being quiet .
Open your mouth .
Open your mouth !
[ grunting ]
[ screaming ]
[ sobbing ]
Okay , Simple .
Oh , I 'm sorry , Ms. Jacqueline .
Now , it 's time ..
... for you to choose a knife .
All you have to do is nod .
No ?
What about this one ?
You don 't like that one either ?
Okay .
How about this one ?
Hmm .
Well ..
... that 's an interesting choice , Simple .
You know ..
... there is something that has been bothering Mr. Sophistication ..
... for quite a bit .
And perhaps it 's more interesting to him ..
... than it would be to you .
But to be honest
he gets pretty fuckin ' pissed when he thinks about it .
Why is it always the man 's fault ?
No matter where you go
it 's like you 're some sort of wandering guilty person .
Without even having harmed a single kitten .
I actually get sad when I think about it .
If one is so unfortunate ..
... as to have been born male ..
... then you 're also born guilty .
Think of the injustice in that .
Women are always the victims , right ?
And men , they are always the criminals .
[ screaming ]
Told you before , this is private property .
I want you to leave .
All the king 's horses and all the king 's men
couldn 't put Simple back together again .
Why are they always so stupid ?
Who 's stupid ?
All the women you kill strike me as seriously unintelligent .
Come on .
I 've also killed men .
But you only talk about the stupid women
unless you think all women are stupid .
Well , the stories I 've told were selected at random , but ...
You feel superior to women and want to brag ?
It turns you on , doesn 't it , Jack ?
No , no , but women are easier .
Not physically , they 're just easier to work with .
More cooperative .
To kill , you mean .
If you like .
Mr. Sophistication believes in that theory .
So , Mr. Sophistication is , uh , the theoretician ?
I can tell you 're lapping it up
when I tell you about Mr. Sophistication .
" So Jack hears voices
" that order him to do this or do that .
Jack must be psychotic . "
I loathe diagnosis you can just write down in letters .
That 's not fair , the letters are clear .
They look after us and create boundaries
between good and evil , and they carry religion .
Religion has ruined human beings
because your God teaches people to deny the tiger in themselves
and turns us all into a throng of slaves
too shameful to acknowledge it .
Oh , Jack , you should have read
the right letters in your life
but you didn 't want to .
♪ Fame fame what you like is in the limo ♪
♪ Fame fame what you get is no tomorrow ♪
The collection of corpses were mostly frozen
shortly after death
however , I think a handful of them , by chance
had reached , uh , at least , a certain degree of putrefaction
before I managed to get them on ice .
Can you say if putrefaction is good or evil ?
Most people would say , it 's the natural breakdown
which , in the end , is a reaction of matter
which is the basis for life on earth .
Thereby , it 's neither particularly good nor evil
and that a human being must be perceived as alive
if you 're to describe that person 's qualities
and identify that person 's ultimate goal .
But this is where Mr. Sophistication
has a very different opinion .
He argues quite well that the ultimate goal
for the human being is not prior to death
but after .
You reduce everything human to matter
and that way life disappears and along with it art
which you value so highly .
Verge , you 're a bitter old bastard .
You kill art by imposing your moral ruler on life
which I want to free
because art is so immeasurably vaster
than we will ever understand .
May I illustrate now ?
There is no avoiding it , is there ?
[ instrumental music ]
I don 't have a handle on how many processes take part
in the decay of a dead human
but I know a bit about dessert wines .
In order to achieve the most sublime sweetness
and the greatest wines , nature has provided us
with various methods .
The three most common forms of decomposition are
frost ..
... dehydration ..
... and a fungus with the enticingly
mysterious name , the noble rot .
The first method is the one that in Germany
is used to produce " Eiswein . "
The method quite simply entails
leaving the grapes on the vine for so long
that they are exposed to frost for a certain number of nights
before they are pressed .
This method increases the sugar content
in the wine dramatically .
It is very risky , as the grapes must have certain qualities
in order to be able to withstand the process .
On top of that , there can be uncertainty
about whether or not the first night 's frost
lives up precisely to the expectations , et cetera .
The second method is called " Trockenbeeren "
in which the grapes are allowed to hang on the vine
until they dry up and very nearly become raisins .
The last method , which , for example
is essential for the production of Sauternes
is a kind of mold that causes grapes
to be very full-bodied
and have an explosively high sugar content .
You could say about all three processes
that it 's the breakdown that lifts the living grape
up to be a part of an artwork .
You can view the processes that start in a human being
after death in the same manner .
Says you ! And I still say that without love there is no art .
It 's not up for debate .
The thing you are talking about with the grapes
is just nature 's method of decomposing .
If decomposition is a way to salvation
then what about your house ?
By God , you cannot convince me
that the idea of your first house being torn down
was , in any way , satisfying .
Do you claim that it was built to be torn down ?
No , of course it wasn 't ideal
and I 'm sorry to say that it happened
no less than three more times
that I started construction and then became doubtful .
It was difficult to create the house
that I had dreamed of .
The material didn 't do what I wanted it to do .
The houses I had drawn had already
at the very first detail , something banal
not to say ordinary , about them
Isn 't that what in art you would call epigonism ?
Your great talent only reached so far
you , artist of all times .
When you were writing , didn 't you yourself plan
the destruction of your most popular literary work ?
" The Aeneid " was a commissioned work
where the ruling power and its ideas were glorified by me
to the point where it was no longer art .
But if glorification could demean a work ..
... why should destruction and demolition
not be able to do the opposite and create art ?
Albert Speer invented " The Theory of Ruin Value "
by examining the Greek and Roman ruins
and constructed his buildings using both weaker
and stronger materials
so that they , in a thousand years , would appear
as aesthetically perfect ruins .
Which fortunately were smashed to atoms
in mere few years after their construction .
Hubris is punished by nemesis
if I may use an old-fashioned expression .
But an artist must be cynical
and not worry about the welfare of humans or Gods in his art .
This talk about the value of ruins
makes it too obvious , not to mention , another subject .
The value of icons .
[ instrumental music ]
[ humming ]
The Stuka
without a doubt the world 's most beautiful airplane
and to top it off featuring an eerily sophisticated detail .
I 'm sure you know what I 'm talking about .
No , by God that has never interested me
but do tell me about it .
The Stuka was a dive-bomber .
They say that the pilots actually passed out
for a brief moment during the actual dive .
But the detail per favore .
Fantastic .
Incomparable .
Notice the sound when the plane dives .
The screeching sound .
A result of poor design if you ask me .
Poor design , please .
On the contrary , the screeching was intrinsic
sirens were attached to the undercarriage of the plane
purposely designed as a psychological act of war .
No one who heard it in action will ever forget that sound .
It made the blood run cold in everyone 's veins .
Known as Jericho 's Trumpet .
Sadistic , but in your eyes
probably a masterpiece .
No , more than a masterpiece .
An icon .
The person or persons , who conceived the Stuka
and its functions , were icon-creators .
What I 'm getting at is this
as disinclined as the world is
to acknowledge the beauty of decay
it 's just as disinclined to give credit to those
no credit to us
who create the real icons of this planet .
We are deemed the ultimate evil .
[ instrumental music ]
All the icons that have had and always will have
an impact on the world
are for me extravagant art .
The noble rot .
Stop it ... you Antichrist !
I don 't recall ever having escorted
a so thoroughly depraved person as you , Jack .
Since you have now apparently set your heart
in mass extermination
let me make a brief comment
about the Buchenwald camp
that emphasizes my attitude towards art and love .
In the middle of this concentration camp stood a tree
and not just any old tree , but an oak
and not just any oak , but the one Goethe
when he was young , sat beneath
and wrote some of humanity 's most important works .
Goethe .
Here you can talk about masterpieces
and the value of icons .
The personification of humanism , dignity
culture and goodness was by the irony of faith
suddenly present
in the middle of one of the all time
greatest crimes against humanity .
Some people claim that the atrocities we commit
in our fiction are those inner desires
which we cannot commit in our controlled civilization .
So they are expressed instead through our art .
I don 't agree .
I believe heaven and hell are one and the same .
The soul belongs to heaven and the body to hell .
The soul is reason and the body is all the dangerous things
for example art and icons .
[ instrumental music ]
Let me finish with a curiosity .
I 've always considered it ridiculous
when I 've heard about the serial killer 's
favorite trophy .
Here you are , Jack .
And yet I let myself be tempted to not let
Simple 's other breast go to waste
but have it prepared and sown .
Also a small icon .
Thank you , sir .
[ crackling ]
[ banging ]
Do you wanna fucking die ?
- No . - Then do what I fucking say .
Do what I say !
Unlock it .
Drop the keys .
Turn around .
Cuff .
Cuff !
[ breathing heavily ]
[ shuddering ]
[ groaning ]
Kneel down .
We 're freezing .
One of the others fainted earlier .
We 're dying of cold .
We 're dying .
Really ? " We 're freezing . "
I guess I owe you gentlemen an explanation .
During World War II on the eastern front
German soldiers had large programs of executions
but were in short supply of ammunition
so they experimented with the execution of several individuals
with one , just one single bullet .
Now as a tribute to that , uh , ingenuity ..
... I 'm going to conduct a small experiment of my own .
I 'm going to use ..
... a full metal jacket bullet
which has the capacity
to pass through each and every one of your heads .
That 's not something that I would be able to do
with basic hunting ammunition .
Wait , wait , wait , wait , sir , sir .
I ... it 's a misunderstanding , sir .
- I hear that a lot . - No , sir .
W ... what I mean is that you are wrong
about the ammunition , sir .
That is not full metal ammunition , sir .
I 'm a military man , and I know , sir .
Fuck .
You 're right ! This is a hunting round .
This box , it 's ... it 's completely mislabeled .
Goddammit !
Forgive me , gentlemen , I 'm gonna have to , uh
step out for a moment .
I know it 's not an ideal situation .
Don 't die on me guys , okay ?
[ tires screeching ]
I 've never yelled at you before , Al
but I 'm about to now .
What does that look like to you , what does that say there ?
Uh , thirty odd six ..
- Thirty odd six , that 's correct . - Yeah .
It also says full metal jacket .
And when I look inside ..
Get me a goddamn box , Al , and this time
make sure it 's got full metal jacket bullets in it !
Is it too much to fucking ask that the contents of the box
match what 's written on the label ?
I can , I can see that the , you 're right
the label doesn 't quite match the ..
... uh , content .
- W ... well , that 's correct . - Yeah , but ..
The thing is that what I can 't see
is that the ... the ..
... the box was bought here in the shop .
Uh ..
Well I buy all my shit here .
I have , for 20 years .
I 'm in here almost every other week .
What 's wrong with you , Al ?
I 'm sorry , I need to see a receipt .
- Receipt ? - Yeah
Well , I don 't have a fuckin ' receipt .
I don 't ever recall getting a receipt here .
Now I 'm in a fucking hurry .
Let me buy a new box .
But this time make sure it contains
full metal jacket bullets .
Okay , uh , c ... can I just see some ID first ?
Don 't fucking do this , Al .
The thing is , the ... the law requires that I have ...
How about this ..
No doubt about your ... your identity ...
Sell me just one full metal jacket bullet .
Can I , can I just ask ..
... why just ... one ?
Well , that will be none of your fuckin ' business .
- That ... that 's right . I 'm sor ... - Okay ?
I do business here because you don 't ask stupid questions .
I 'm ... I 'm sorry , Jack . I 'm ... I 'm sorry .
- Shut it down , Al , go home , have a sandwich . - Okay .
You 've lost your fucking mind , Al .
Yeah . I 'm sorry . I 'm so ..
♪ Is it any wonder
♪ I reject you first fame fame ♪
Fuck you , Al !
♪ Is it any wonder you are too cool to fool ? ♪
♪ Fame
[ engine revving ]
♪ Fame bully for you chilly for me ♪
♪ Got to get a rain check on pain ♪
♪ Fame
Al 's gone totally bonkers .
I need a full metal jacket cartridge .
Yesterday , the police visited Al
and then me
with lights and sirens
to get you .
It 's over now , Jack .
What 's over ?
They know what you 've done .
We ..
Alright , what have I done ?
The robbery .
Robbery ?
You guys better fucking get it together .
I haven 't robbed anybody .
This is ridiculous .
I 'm gonna call the police , Jack .
Give me your gun .
I don 't run around with guns on me .
This is , this is crazy .
Sit yourself down , Jack .
This is S.P.
I wanna get ahold of Rob .
Well , when you get hold of him , you 'll tell him
to get over here straight away .
I 've caught Jack .
I 'm kind of glad that you are the one that caught me .
Perhaps you don 't know this ..
... but I think of you as my best friend .
Now that might not be a big deal to you ..
... but you 've meant a great deal to me .
It feels quite nice knowing that it 's all over .
Somebody had to free me
and stop me from stealing things that don 't belong to me .
And that someone turned out to be you .
Do you remember the time you took down that eight pointer
that I 'd been tracking for four days ?
It was on my territory for sure .
No one 's questioning that .
You 've always been a great shot .
Now would you , uh , quit pointing that gun at me ?
Kind of hurting my feelings a little bit .
I 'm not going anywhere .
After all you know me , S.P.
Yeah .
I know you .
And you 've never lied to me .
No .
Just as fast as I always was , huh ?
You wouldn 't make it to the door .
[ sniffles ]
What have I done ?
[ sighs ]
[ laughs ]
[ choking ]
[ siren wailing ]
You got him , S.P.
Well , I 'll take it from here .
[ gunshots ]
[ siren wailing ]
[ tires screeching ]
[ shuddering ]
Can we agree on this ?
Is that a full metal jacket cartridge ?
Yes , sir . That is ..
That is a full metal jacket rifle cartridge .
Oh , please , please
please , don 't do this , please .
- Alright , come on . - Don 't do it , please !
[ men shuddering ]
No , no .
I can 't focus .
It 's too close .
[ siren wailing ]
[ groans ]
[ sighs ]
[ grunting ]
[ clanking ]
[ siren wailing ]
[ men groaning ]
[ breathing heavily ]
Perfect .
Jack !
Who are you ?
Call me Verge .
How did you get in here ?
What do you want ?
As I see it , it 's you who called me .
I 've been with you for a while , you just didn 't notice me .
[ instrumental music ]
So , did you come here to stop me ?
I haven 't come here to stop you from anything .
I just have one question .
What 's the question ?
Wasn 't there something about you building a house ?
Wasn 't Jack going to build a house ?
[ sighs ]
Yes .
I ... I ... I was ..
... trying ..
... but I didn 't get very far .
This is the police .
Come out with your hands where we can see them
I can see it 's going to be a bit difficult
to get that house built , but perhaps another one .
Think , Jack , after all you are an engineer
and call yourself an architect .
I 've been told you have an interesting theory
about the material
which you claim has its own will .
Find the material , Jack
and let it do the work .
[ humming ]
[ piano music ]
[ singing in foreign language ]
Your house is a fine little house , Jack .
It 's absolutely usable .
[ whirring ]
Are you coming , Jack ?
[ gunshot ]
I 'm here ... Jack .
May I ask you something ?
I can 't promise I 'll answer .
R ... right , that is exactly what I meant .
Um , are you allowed to speak along the way ?
I was thinking there might be rules .
Put it this way
very few make it all the way without uttering a word .
People are overcome with a strange
and sudden need to confess on these trips .
And not all of it can be said
to be of great rhetorical quality
but do carry on merrily
just don 't believe you 're going to tell me something
I haven 't heard before .
[ instrumental music ]
[ music continues ]
[ buzzing ]
Do you hear a buzzing sound ?
Yes .
And I don 't think you want to know
where it 's coming from .
I wanna know everything .
For thousands of years human beings
have tried to localize hell .
Among other methods
by seeking the sound it generates .
One shouldn 't focus on extracting screams and wailing
because the cries of pain of so many millions
of individuals together ..
... becomes what you have just heard .
A buzzing sound whose intensity
will increase as we get ever closer
to the presence of suffering .
[ watermill creaking ]
[ intense music ]
Verge ?
I 'm here , Jack .
I don 't feel so good , Verge .
There 's a sour taste in my mouth .
You want me to show you the way to the next whiskey bar ?
[ instrumental music ]
[ music continues ]
[ crickets chirping ]
[ rustling ]
Those are the Elysian Fields .
We don 't have access here .
[ men exhaling ]
[ exhaling continues ]
[ exhaling ]
[ men exhaling ]
[ inhaling ]
[ exhaling ]
[ intense music ]
[ eerie music ]
[ music continues ]
That 's how deep the deepest hell goes .
It 's actually not here I 'm to deliver you ..
... however improbable that may sound ..
... but a couple of circles higher up .
I took you down here as a kind of a favor ..
... because you did after all give me a little to chew on
with your story , and I understood
that you wanted to see it all .
When you are done looking , we 'll turn back .
Where does that path lead ?
On the other side .
It leads out of hell and up .
As you can see there was once a bridge
but that was before my time .
Isn 't it possible to climb all the way around ?
This way ..
... and make it over to the other side ?
Quite a few have tried , but I have to say ..
... never successfully .
I wouldn 't recommend it
but the choice is entirely yours .
I 'll take my chance .
Bye , Jack .
Bye , Verge .
[ grunts ]
[ groaning ]
[ panting ]
[ grunts ]
[ screams ]
[ instrumental music ]
♪ Hit the road Jack and don 't you come back ♪
♪ No more no more no more no more ♪
♪ Hit the road Jack
♪ And don 't you come back no more ♪
♪ Oh what you said ?
♪ Hit the road Jack
♪ And don 't you come back
♪ No more no more no more no more ♪
♪ Hit the road Jack
♪ And don 't you come back no more ♪
♪ Old woman old woman don 't you treat me so mean ♪
♪ You 're the meanest old woman I have ever seen ♪
♪ I guess if you say so
♪ I 'll have to pack my things and go ♪
♪ That 's right
♪ Hit the road Jack
♪ And don 't you come back
♪ No more no more no more no more ♪
♪ Hit the road Jack
♪ And don 't you come back no more ♪
♪ Oh what 'd you say ?
♪ Hit the road Jack
♪ And don 't you come back
♪ No more no more no more no more ♪
♪ Hit the road Jack
♪ And don 't you come back no more ♪
♪ Oh baby oh baby don 't you treat me this way ♪
♪ ' Cause I 'll get back on my feet some day ♪
♪ I don 't care if you do ' cause it 's understood ♪
♪ You ain 't got no money you just ain 't no good ♪
♪ Well I guess if you say so
♪ I 'll have to pack my things and go ♪
♪ That 's right
♪ Hit the road Jack
♪ And don 't you come back
♪ No more no more no more no more ♪
♪ Hit the road Jack
♪ And don 't you come back no more ♪
♪ What 's that ? ♪ What 'd you call me ?
♪ You are ridiculous ♪ What ?
♪ Why don 't you just pack your little suitcases ♪
♪ And go on back to Bogalusa ♪ Yeah
♪ Well I just may do that baby ♪
♪ I 'll just may go hit the road ♪
♪ And try to find myself
♪ You find yourself ?
♪ Well if you do and when you do ♪
♪ Get lost ♪ Who me ?
♪ That 's right ♪ Hit the road Jack
♪ And don 't you come back
♪ No more no more no more no more ♪
♪ Hit the road Jack
♪ And don 't you come back no more ♪
♪ Oh what 'd you say ?
♪ Hit the road Jack
♪ And don 't you come back
♪ No more no more no more no more ♪
♪ Hit the road Jack
♪ And don 't you come back
♪ No more no more no more no more ♪
♪ Hit the road Jack
♪ And don 't you come back no more ♪
♪ Oh what 'd you say ?
♪ Hit the road Jack
♪ And don 't you come back
♪ No more no more no more no more ♪
♪ Hit the road Jack
♪ And don 't you come back
♪ No more no more no more no more ♪
♪ Hit the road Jack
♪ And don 't you come back no more ♪
♪ Oh what 'd you say ?
♪ Hit the road Jack
♪ And don 't you come back
♪ No more no more no more no more ♪
♪ Hit the road Jack
♪ And don 't you come back no more ♪
♪ Don 't you come back no more ♪ Oh baby please
♪ Don 't you come back no more
♪ You cannot do this to me
♪ Oh baby please
♪ Don 't you come back no more
♪ Oh oh baby please
♪ Oh baby please ♪ Don 't you come back no more
♪ Don 't you come back no more
♪ Don 't you come back no more ♪ Oh baby please
♪ You cannot do this to me ♪ Don 't you come back no more
♪ Oh baby please ♪ Don 't you come back no more
♪ Don 't you come back no more
♪ Oh oh oh baby
♪ Don 't you come back no more ♪ Oh baby please
♪ Don 't you come back no more
♪ Don 't you come back no more ♪ ♪